{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Extreme old age when a man behaves like a fool", "opta": "Imbecility", "optb": "Senility", "optc": "Dotage", "optd": "Superannuation", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "That which cannot be corrected", "opta": "Unintelligible", "optb": "Indelible", "optc": "Illegible", "optd": "Incorrigible", "ans": "D", "explanation": "Incorrigible (Adjective): (of a person or their tendencies) Not able to be corrected, improved, or reformed."}, {"question": "The study of ancient societies", "opta": "Anthropology", "optb": "Archaeology", "optc": "History", "optd": "Ethnology", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person of good understanding knowledge and reasoning power", "opta": "Expert", "optb": "Intellectual", "optc": "Snob", "optd": "Literate", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person who insists on something", "opta": "Disciplinarian", "optb": "Stickler", "optc": "Instantaneous", "optd": "Boaster", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "State in which the few govern the many", "opta": "Monarchy", "optb": "Oligarchy", "optc": "Plutocracy", "optd": "Autocracy", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A style in which a writer makes a display of his knowledge", "opta": "Pedantic", "optb": "Verbose", "optc": "Pompous", "optd": "Ornate", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "List of the business or subjects to be considered at a meeting", "opta": "Schedule", "optb": "Timetable", "optc": "Agenda", "optd": "Plan", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Leave or remove from a place considered dangerous", "opta": "Evade", "optb": "Evacuate", "optc": "Avoid", "optd": "Exterminate", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A prima facie case is such", "opta": "As it seems at first sight", "optb": "As it is made to seem at first sight", "optc": "As it turns out to be at the end", "optd": "As it seems to the court after a number of hearings", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person pretending to be somebody he is not", "opta": "Magician", "optb": "Rogue", "optc": "Liar", "optd": "Imposter", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person who knows many foreign languages", "opta": "Linguist", "optb": "Grammarian", "optc": "Polyglot", "optd": "Bilingual", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who has little faith in human sincerity and goodness", "opta": "Egoist", "optb": "Fatalist", "optc": "Stoic", "optd": "Cynic", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who possesses many talents", "opta": "Versatile", "optb": "Nubile", "optc": "Exceptional", "optd": "Gifted", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Words inscribed on tomb", "opta": "Epitome", "optb": "Epistle", "optc": "Epilogue", "optd": "Epitaph", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who eats everything", "opta": "Omnivorous", "optb": "Omniscient", "optc": "Irrestible", "optd": "Insolvent", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Malafide case is one", "opta": "Which is undertaken in a good faith", "optb": "Which is undertaken in a bad faith", "optc": "Which is undertaken after a long delay", "optd": "Which is not undertaken at all", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The custom or practice of having more than one husband at same time", "opta": "Polygyny", "optb": "Polyphony", "optc": "Polyandry", "optd": "Polychromy", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Tending to move away from the centre or axis", "opta": "Centrifugal", "optb": "Centripetal", "optc": "Axiomatic", "optd": "Awry", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Teetotaller means", "opta": "One who abstains from theft", "optb": "One who abstains from meat", "optc": "One who abstains from taking wine", "optd": "One who abstains from malice", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person interested in collecting, studying and selling of old things", "opta": "Antiquarian", "optb": "Junk-dealer", "optc": "Crank", "optd": "Archealogist", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A drawing on transparent paper", "opta": "Red print", "optb": "Blue print", "optc": "Negative", "optd": "Transparency", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who is not easily pleased by anything", "opta": "Maiden", "optb": "Mediaeval", "optc": "Precarious", "optd": "Fastidious", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A remedy for all diseases", "opta": "Stoic", "optb": "Marvel", "optc": "Panacea", "optd": "Recompense", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who is fond of fighting", "opta": "Bellicose", "optb": "Aggressive", "optc": "Belligerent", "optd": "Militant", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A small shop that sells fashionable clothes, cosmetics, etc.", "opta": "Store", "optb": "Stall", "optc": "Boutique", "optd": "Booth", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "That which cannot be read", "opta": "Negligible", "optb": "Illegible", "optc": "Ineligible", "optd": "Incorrigible", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a state of tension or anxiety or suspense", "opta": "Off balance", "optb": "Depressed", "optc": "Diffused", "optd": "On tenterhooks", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "That which cannot be seen", "opta": "Insensible", "optb": "Intangible", "optc": "Invisible", "optd": "Unseen", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To slap with a flat object", "opta": "Chop", "optb": "Hew", "optc": "Gnaw", "optd": "Swat", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Habitually silent or talking little", "opta": "Servile", "optb": "Unequivocal", "optc": "Taciturn", "optd": "Synoptic", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Taciturn means tending to be silent and uncommunicative, reticent."}, {"question": "One who cannot be corrected", "opta": "Incurable", "optb": "Incorrigible", "optc": "Hardened", "optd": "Invulnerable", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Be the embodiment or perfect example of", "opta": "Characterise", "optb": "Idol", "optc": "Personify", "optd": "Signify", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person not sure of the existence of god", "opta": "Cynic", "optb": "Agnostic", "optc": "Atheist", "optd": "Theist", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A paper written by hand", "opta": "Handicraft", "optb": "Manuscript", "optc": "Handiwork", "optd": "Thesis", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The act of violating the sanctity of the church is", "opta": "Blashphemy", "optb": "Heresy", "optc": "Sacrilege", "optd": "Desecration", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Something that can be heard", "opta": "Auditory", "optb": "Audio-visual", "optc": "Audible", "optd": "Audition", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A name adopted by an author in his writings", "opta": "Nickname", "optb": "Pseudonym", "optc": "Nomenclature", "optd": "Title", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Study of birds", "opta": "Orology", "optb": "Optology", "optc": "Ophthalmology", "optd": "Ornithology", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A place that provides refuge", "opta": "Asylum", "optb": "Sanatorium", "optc": "Shelter", "optd": "Orphanage", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A child born after death of his father", "opta": "Posthumous", "optb": "Orphan", "optc": "Bastard", "optd": "Progenitor", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The absence of law and order", "opta": "Rebellion", "optb": "Anarchy", "optc": "Mutiny", "optd": "Revolt", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The raison d'etre of a controversy is", "opta": "The enthusiasm with which it is kept alive", "optb": "The fitness with which participants handle it", "optc": "The reason or justification of its existence", "optd": "The unending hostility the parties concerned have towards each other", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A place where bees are kept in called", "opta": "An apiary", "optb": "A mole", "optc": "A hive", "optd": "A sanctury", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A religious discourse", "opta": "Preach", "optb": "Stanza", "optc": "Sanctorum", "optd": "Sermon", "ans": "D", "explanation": "A talk on a religious or moral subject, especially one given during a church service and based on a passage from the Bible."}, {"question": "Parts of a country behind the coast or a river's banks", "opta": "Isthmus", "optb": "Archipelago", "optc": "Hinterland", "optd": "Swamps", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Study of the evolution of man as an animal", "opta": "Archaeology", "optb": "Anthropology", "optc": "Chronology", "optd": "Ethnology", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person who speaks many languages", "opta": "Linguist", "optb": "Monolingual", "optc": "Polyglot", "optd": "Bilingual", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who does not believe in existence of god", "opta": "Egoist", "optb": "Atheist", "optc": "Stoic", "optd": "Naive", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A disease of mind causing an uncontrollable desire to steal", "opta": "Schizophrenia", "optb": "Claustrophobia", "optc": "Kleptomania", "optd": "Magolomania", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who sacrifices his life for a cause", "opta": "Patriot", "optb": "Martyr", "optc": "Revolutionary", "optd": "Soldier", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person who brings goods illegally into the country", "opta": "Importer", "optb": "Exporter", "optc": "Fraud", "optd": "Smuggler", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To take secretly in small quantities", "opta": "Robbery", "optb": "Pilferage", "optc": "Theft", "optd": "Defalcation", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To accustom oneself to a foreign climate", "opta": "Adapt", "optb": "Adopt", "optc": "Accustom", "optd": "Acclimatise", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who knows everything", "opta": "Literate", "optb": "Scholar", "optc": "Omnipotent", "optd": "Omniscient", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Detailed plan of journey", "opta": "Travelogue", "optb": "Travelkit", "optc": "Schedule", "optd": "Itinerary", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Giving undue favours to one's own kith and kin", "opta": "Nepotism", "optb": "Favouritism", "optc": "Wordliness", "optd": "Corruption", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Hater of learning and knowledge", "opta": "Misologist", "optb": "Bibliophile", "optc": "Misogynist", "optd": "Misanthropist", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person interested in reading books and nothing else", "opta": "Book-keepr", "optb": "Scholar", "optc": "Book-worm", "optd": "Student", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A place where monks live as a secluded community", "opta": "Cathedral", "optb": "Diocese", "optc": "Convent", "optd": "Monastery", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Incapable of being seen through", "opta": "Ductile", "optb": "Opaque", "optc": "Obsolete", "optd": "Potable", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who does not care for literature or art", "opta": "Primitive", "optb": "Illiterate", "optc": "Philistine", "optd": "Barbarian", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A large sleeping-room with many beds", "opta": "Bedroom", "optb": "Dormitory", "optc": "Hostel", "optd": "Basement", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Continuing fight between parties, families, clans, etc.", "opta": "Enmity", "optb": "Feud", "optc": "Quarrel", "optd": "Skirmish", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A building for storing threshed grain", "opta": "Hangar", "optb": "Dockyard", "optc": "Store", "optd": "Granary", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Policeman riding on motorcycles as guards to a VIP", "opta": "Outriders", "optb": "Servants", "optc": "Commandos", "optd": "Attendants", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who is determined to exact full vengeance for wrongs done to him", "opta": "Virulent", "optb": "Vindictive", "optc": "Usurer", "optd": "Vindicator", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Murder of a king", "opta": "Infanticide", "optb": "Matricide", "optc": "Genocide", "optd": "Regicide", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An expression of mild disapproval", "opta": "Warning", "optb": "Denigration", "optc": "Impertinence", "optd": "Reproof", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One absorbed in his own thoughts and feelings rather than in things outside", "opta": "Scholar", "optb": "Recluse", "optc": "Introvert", "optd": "Intellectual", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who dabbles in fine arts for the love of it and not for monetary gains", "opta": "Connoisseur", "optb": "Amateur", "optc": "Professional", "optd": "Dilettante", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A school boy who cuts classes frequently is a", "opta": "Defeatist", "optb": "Sycophant", "optc": "Truant", "optd": "Martinet", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Ready to believe", "opta": "Credulous", "optb": "Credible", "optc": "Creditable", "optd": "Incredible", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Medical study of skin and its diseases", "opta": "Dermatology", "optb": "Endocrinology", "optc": "Gynealogy", "optd": "Orthopaedics", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A person who tries to deceive people by claiming to be able to do wonderful things", "opta": "Trickster", "optb": "Imposter", "optc": "Magician", "optd": "Mountebank", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A dramatic performance", "opta": "Mask", "optb": "Mosque", "optc": "Masque", "optd": "Mascot", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who does not marry, especially as a religious obligation", "opta": "Bachelor", "optb": "Celibate", "optc": "Vigin", "optd": "Recluse", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "That which is perceptible by touch is", "opta": "Contagious", "optb": "Contingent", "optc": "Tenacious", "optd": "Tangible", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Very pleasing to eat", "opta": "Appetising", "optb": "Palatable", "optc": "Tantalising", "optd": "Sumptuous", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The part of government which is concerned with making of rules", "opta": "Court", "optb": "Tribunal", "optc": "Bar", "optd": "Legislature", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who believes that all things and events in life are predetermined is a", "opta": "Fatalist", "optb": "Puritan", "optc": "Egoist", "optd": "Tyrant", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Something that relates to everyone in the world", "opta": "General", "optb": "Common", "optc": "Usual", "optd": "Universal", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To walk with slow or regular Steps is to", "opta": "Limp", "optb": "Stride", "optc": "Pace", "optd": "Advance", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A style full of words", "opta": "Verbose", "optb": "Pedantic", "optc": "Rhetorical", "optd": "Abundant", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Murder of a brother", "opta": "Patricide", "optb": "Regicide", "optc": "Homicide", "optd": "Fratricide", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Having superior or intellectual interests and tastes", "opta": "Elite", "optb": "Highbrow", "optc": "Sophisticated", "optd": "Fastidious", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To cause troops, etc. to spread out in readiness for battle", "opta": "Disperse", "optb": "Deploy", "optc": "Collocate", "optd": "Align", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A voice loud enough to be heard", "opta": "Audible", "optb": "Applaudable", "optc": "Laudable", "optd": "Oral", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A light sailing boat built specially for racing", "opta": "Canoe", "optb": "Yacht", "optc": "Frigate", "optd": "Dinghy", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who is in charge of museum", "opta": "Curator", "optb": "Supervisor", "optc": "Caretaker", "optd": "Warden", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A government by the nobles", "opta": "Aristocracy", "optb": "Democracy", "optc": "Autocracy", "optd": "Bureaucracy", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One who is honourably discharged from service", "opta": "Retired", "optb": "Emeritus", "optc": "Relieved", "optd": "Emancipated", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Present opposing arguments or evidence", "opta": "Criticise", "optb": "Rebuff", "optc": "Reprimand", "optd": "Rebut", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The policy of extending a country's empire and influence", "opta": "Communism", "optb": "Internationalism", "optc": "Capitalism", "optd": "Imperialism", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Of outstanding significance", "opta": "Monumental", "optb": "Rational", "optc": "Ominous", "optd": "Evident", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Code of diplomatic etiquette and precedence", "opta": "Statesmanship", "optb": "Formalism", "optc": "Hierarchy", "optd": "Protocol", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A fixed orbit in space in relation to earth", "opta": "Geological", "optb": "Geo-synchronous", "optc": "Geo-centric", "optd": "Geo-stationary", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "That which cannot be believed", "opta": "Incredible", "optb": "Incredulous", "optc": "Implausible", "optd": "Unreliable", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To issue a thunderous verbal attack", "opta": "Languish", "optb": "Animate", "optc": "Fulminate", "optd": "Invigorate", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}